A Guide to the Virginia Electric and Power Company Records, 1849-ca. 1995
Library of Virginia
- General Counsel and Vice President Files, 1887-1942, 14.4 cubic feet (Box 1-32)
  - Legal Files, 1903-1942, 11.475 cubic feet (Box 3-27)
    - Richmond and Rappahannock Railway Company, agreement with, April 1912 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Richmond and Rappahannock Railway Company, agreement with, [?] May 1912 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - Richmond and Rappahannock Railway Company, agreement with, [?] May 1912 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Richmond and Rappahannock Railway Company, agreement with, 2-22 May 1912 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Richmond and Rappahannock Railway Company, agreement with, June-October 1912 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Richmond and Rappahannock Railway Company, agreement with, 1913-1920 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Richmond Ice Delivery Corporation, case of, 1921-1922 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Richmond Interurban Line, express service rates and operation, 1912-1919 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Richmond Interurban Line, fare increases, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Richmond Interurban Line, fare increases, 1917-1918 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Richmond Interurban Line, State Corporation Commission and stops along, 1912-1916 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Richmond Public Utilities, purchase of, 1913 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Richmond railway station, location of, 1913-1916 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Richmond, Sol, case of, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Richmond Wood Working Company, case of, 1916-1917 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Riddick, Joseph, case of, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Riddick, Sarah Francis, case of, 1917 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Riverside Park lots (Norfolk), dedication of, 1914 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Roar, Martha and Charlie, case of, 1921-1922 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Rochelle, Carl, case of, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Rogers, Lily (administrator of William Rogers), case of, 1918-1919 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Rolling-stock tax, as applies to electrical railways, 1912 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Root, J. T., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Rosenberg, Alice, case of, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Rosenkrans, A. S., case of, 1918 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Ruckle, Frank, case of, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Rudd, L. E., case of, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Russell, Henry F., case of, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Russell, Lula P., case of, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Cases: General - S, 1922-1923 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Cases: General - S, 1924 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Cases: General - S, 1925 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - St. Clair, J. L., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Sallinger, W. S., case of, 1917 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Salmon, R. R., case of, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Samler, D., case of, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Sauer, C. F., case of, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Sauls, A. W., case of, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Saunders, George, case of, 1915 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Saunders, M. C., case of, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Saunders, R. E., case of, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Savage, George, case of, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Saxton, George, case of, 1917 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Schaefer, Mary, case of, 1915-1916 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Schneider, Maude Estelle, case of, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Schwartz, Carrie, case of, 1921-1923 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Seaboard Airline Railway Company, case of, 1920-1921 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Sears, R. J., case of, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Segel, F. case of, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Seiderman and Kraemer, case of, 1918-1919 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Selby, William, case of, 1919 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Selph, R. E., case of, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Shackleford, S. E., case of, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Shames, Max, case of, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Shapiro, S., case of, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Shultz, Walter R., case of, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Shumate, Ellen, case of, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Silver, M. and H., case of, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Simmons, Martha (administrator of Jefferson D. Simmons), case of, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Simpson, Charles A., case of, 1916 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Simpson, John R., case of, 1915 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Sims, Katie, case of, 1916 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Sitterson, William R., case of, 1923-1924 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Small, B. T., case of, 1918-1919 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Smith, A. R., case of (B1679), 1919 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Smith, A. R., case of (B1790), 1920 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Smith and Hicks, Inc., case of, 1917-1921 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Smith and Welton, case of, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Archie, case of, 1916 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Smith, Bessie, case of, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Smith, G. Mason, case of, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Smith, George Washington, case of, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Smith, H. Garrett, case of, 1919-1922 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Smith, H. M., billing of, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Smith, John J., case of, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Smith, L. F., case of, 1923 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Smith, Luther C., indemnifying bond, 1913 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Smith, Melvin, case of, 1923 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Smith, Nellie, case of, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Smith, Oscar, case of, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Smith, Russell, case of, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Smith, William T., case of, 1917-1918 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Snellings, H. W., case of, 1922 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Snellings, W. W., case of, 1915 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Snyder Brothers, case of, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Snyder, George J., case of, 1921-1924 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Snyder, George J., case of (brief), 1921 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Sommermeyer, G. V., case of, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Soultatus, F. F., case of, 1922 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Southern Laundry Company, case of, 1915 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Southern Railway Company, case of, 1916 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Southern Railway Company, demurrage payment, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Southern Railway, permission to extend, 1911 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Southern Railway Company, property acquisition (Richmond), 1915 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Southern Transportation Company, case of, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Spain, W. L., case of, 1922 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Spear, H. P., case of, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Spencer, C. F., case of, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Spilman, R. S., case of, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Spirt, M., case of, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Stagg, Thomas E., case of, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Standard Paper Manufacturing Company, agreement with, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Stanley, J. E., case of, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Starnes, Sarah E., case of, 1920, 1924 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - State Corporation Commission, complaints concerning condition of tracks, electrical outages, etc., 1911-1914 (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - State Corporation Commission, complaints concerning condition of tracks, electrical outages, etc., September-November 1918 (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - State Corporation Commission, complaints concerning condition of tracks, electrical outages, etc., December 1918-January 1919 (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - State Corporation Commission proposed freight classification for rail cars, case of, 1905 (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Stephenson, John H., case of, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Stephenson, Q. J., case of, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Steward, Ella, case of, 1922 (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Stokes, Frank, case of, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Stone, J. M., case of, 1923 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Stone, S. Gordon, case of, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Strader, J. S., case of, 1921-1922 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Strange, Harriett, case of, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Street and track construction and right-of-way (Richmond), 1904-1910 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Street and track construction and right-of-way (Richmond), 1904-1911, 1911-1916 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Styron, Thomas W., case of, 1921-1922 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Swain, Estella M., case of, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Swain, G. D., case of, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Sweede, Ella, case of, 1916 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Sweet, James T., case of, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Swinson, Alice, case of, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Sykes, Ida Lee, case of, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Sykes, Mary E., case of, 1915 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Cases: General - T, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Cases: General - T, 1924 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Cases: General - T, 1925 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Tall, Edward A., case of, 1915 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Talley, P. K., case of, 1923-1924 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Tate, A. L., case of, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Taxes on express line earnings in Manchester, 1912 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Taylor, Herbert Earl, case of, 1916-1917 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Taylor, Job, case of, 1921-1922 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Taylor, P. R., case of, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Taylor, Robert Bowman (administrator for Dorothy Hunter Taylor), case of, 1918 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Taylor, William A., case of, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - 10th and Main Street (Richmond) gas explosion, case of, 1920-1921 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Texas Company, case of, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Thaniel, Jackson, case of, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Thayer, Alice Barksdale, case of, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Thayer, William H., case of, 1919 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Thomas, Harry L., case of, 1916 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Thomas, J. T., case of, 1915-1916 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Thomas, James, case of, 1918 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Thomas, William, case of, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Thompson, Alice, case of, 1919 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Thompson, Rose, case of, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Thorogood, James F., case of, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Timberlake, S. L., case of, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Todd, Thomas J., case of, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Toobert, E., case of, 1916 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Tredegar Company, case of, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Tucker, Grace, case of, 1915 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Turnbull, A. R., case of, 1918 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Turner, Archie, case of, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Turner, W. E., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - 20th Street (Norfolk) paving, 1914 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - 21st and Hull Street (Richmond), Atlantic Coast Line Railroad accident, case of, 1918-1921 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - 26th Street (Norfolk) paving, 1913 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Tyler, W. N., case of, 1916 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Tyree, Emma S. (administrator for William Henry Tyree), case of, 1919 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Cases: General - U, 1925 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Umber, Effie, case of, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - United States Fidelity and Guaranty Company, case of, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Cases: General - V, 1924 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Valentine, Fred S., case of, 1917-1918 (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Van Collon, Lawrence D., case of, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Vaughan, Edith A., case of, 1921-1922 (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Vickeres, H. T. (administrator for L. R. Vickeres), case of, 1916 (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - Viett, George F., case of, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - Virginia Smelting Company, State Corporation Commission hearing, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - Cases: General - W, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Cases: General - W, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Cases: General - W, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Wadell, R. E., case of, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Walker, T. C., case of, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Walker, Viola (administrator for Frank Walker), case of, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Wardell, Minnie, case of, 1921 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Washington, Cephus, case of, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Wasserman, E., case of, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Waterman, J. K., case of, 1911-1912 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Waymack, J. E., case of, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Weber, Mamie, case of, 1922 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Webster, E. S., case of, 1921 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Weiner, Abe, case of, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Weiss, S., case of, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Wellons, J. D., case of, 1919-1921 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - West, Mabel, case of, 1917 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Westary, Joseph, case of, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Westhampton Line (Richmond), right-of-way agreement, 1914 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Whitaker, D. W., case of, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Whidbee, Isaac, case of, 1921 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - White, Frank, case of, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - White, Hattie, case of, 1917 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - White, John H., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - White, Lewis, case of, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - White, M. R., case of, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Whitehurst, Herbert C., case of, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Whitehurst, James, case of, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Whitehurst, Lillian (administrator for H. L. Whitehurst), case of, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Whitehurst, Lillian (administrator for Harold L. Whitehurst), case of, 1921-1923 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Whitehurst, Moses, case of, 1915 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Whitlock, Helen A., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Wilburn, A. R., case of, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Wilkins, H. Lewis, case of, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Wilkinson, Frank, case of, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Wilkinson, K. M., case of, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Wilkinson, Wiley F., case of, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Williams, Cornelius, case of, 1916-1917 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Williams, Dora, case of, 1921-1922 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Williams, H. P., case of, 1920-1921 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Williams, J. P., case of, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Williams, J. R., case of, 1921 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Williams, Kathleen Damron, case of, 1920-1921 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Williams, Rosa, case of, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Williams, Willie, case of, 1921-1922 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Willis, Helene M., case of, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Willis, Patrick, case of, 1921 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Wilson, J. W., case of, 1917 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Wilson, J. R., case of, 1921 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Windom, Jesse F., case of, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Winfield, Joseph (administrator of David R. Winfield), case of, 1921-1922 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Wingfield, G. A., case of, 1915 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Wingfield, H. B., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Womble, Sadie M., case of, 1918 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Woods, Hubert, case of, 1915 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Woodward and Son, property transaction, 1915-1916 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Woodward, James F., case of, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Woody, George D., case of, 1915-1916 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Wooten, E. C., case of, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Wray, Ethel Corbin, case of, 1921 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Wright, Ada Jackson, case of, 1920-1922 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Wright, L., case of, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Wright, Peter, case of, 1915 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Wyatt, Alice K., case of, 1920-1922 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Wyron, Israel, case of, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Yarborough, Susan A., case of, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Yasgour, Louis, case of, 1917 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Yavner, L., case of, 1915 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - York, Michael, case of (B1097), 1916 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - York, Michael, case of (B1191), 1917 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Young, Lelia, case of, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Young, Melvin R., case of, 1918-1919 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Young, Mercer, case of, 1917 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Cases: General - Z, 1923-1924 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Ziskind, Theodore, case of, 1921-1922 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Summaries and lists of cases, November 1921 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Summaries and lists of cases, December 1921-February 1922 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Summaries and lists of cases, March-May 1922 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Summaries and lists of cases, June-August 1922 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Summaries and lists of cases, September-November 1922 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Summaries and lists of cases, December 1922-February 1923 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Summaries and lists of cases, March-May 1923 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Summaries and lists of cases, June-August 1923 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Summaries and lists of cases, September-November 1923 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Financial Files, 1888, 1911-1942, 1.52 cubic feet (Box 28-30)
    Consists of correspondence, reports, and other legal documents concerning the Legal Department's expenses and its attempt to establish electricity rates in Richmond; correspondence and weekly and monthly reports of the Light and Power Department; monthly reports of the Transportaion Department and the Motor Transit Corporation; charts of authorized expenditures; and a copy of a Report on the Determination of Original Cost of Electric Plant (1942). There are also receipts, 1888, for the purchase of coal by the company.
    Boxes 28-29 are alphabetical by folder title and then chronologically with folder contents arranged in reverse chronological order. Box 30 contains oversize items and is also alphabetical by folder title and then chronologically with folder contents in reverse chronological order.
    - Authorized expenditures (chart), October 1914-August 1915 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Authorized expenditures (chart), September 1915-February 1916 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Authorized expenditures (chart), March-August 1916 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Authorized expenditures (chart), September-December 1916 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Authorized expenditures (chart), January-May 1917 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Authorized expenditures (chart), June-September 1917 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Authorized expenditures (chart), October 1917-April 1918 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Authorized expenditures(chart), June-August 1918 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Coal receipts, Apr.-May 1888 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Electricity rates in Richmond, Legal Department matters concerning, March 1914 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Electricity rates in Richmond, Legal Department matters concerning, June 1914 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Electricity rates in Richmond, Legal Department matters concerning, September-October 1914 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Electricity rates in Richmond, Legal Department matters concerning, November 1914 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Electricity rates in Richmond, Legal Department matters concerning, 1-15 December 1914 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Electricity rates in Richmond, Legal Department matters concerning, 18-31 December 1914 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Electricity rates in Richmond, Legal Department matters concerning, 2-11 January 1915 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Electricity rates in Richmond, Legal Department matters concerning, 12 January 1915 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Electricity rates in Richmond, Legal Department matters concerning, 12 January-15 February 1915 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Electricity rates in Richmond, Legal Department matters concerning, 15-24 February 1915 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Electricity rates in Richmond, Legal Department matters concerning, 25 February-15 April 1915 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Electricity rates in Richmond, Legal Department matters concerning, 15 April-14 August 1915 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Electricity rates in Richmond, Legal Department matters concerning, April-September 1916 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Electricity rates in Richmond, Legal Department matters concerning, November 1916-September 1918 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Electricity rates in Richmond, Legal Department matters concerning, n. d. (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Estimated cash requirements, 1916, 1919 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Legal Department expenses, correspondence, 1911-1921 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Light and Power Department, operating expenses report, 1914 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, June 1916, April 1917 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 1-8 January 1921 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 15-22 January 1921 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 29 January-5 February 1921 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 12-19 February 1921 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 26 February-5 March 1921 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 12-19 March 1921 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 26 March-2 April 1921 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 9-23 April 1921 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 16 April-7 May 1921 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 30 April-14 May 1921 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 21-28 May 1921 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 4-18 June 1921 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 11-25 June 1921 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 2-9 July 1921 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 16-23 July 1921 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 30 July-6 August 1921 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 13-20 August 1921 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 27 August-3 September 1921 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 10-24 September 1921 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 17 September-1 October 1921 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 8-15 October 1921 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 22-29 October 1921 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 5-12 November 1921 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 19-26 November 1921 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 3-10 December 1921 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 17-24 December 1921 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 31 December 1921-7 January 1922 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 14-28 January 1922 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 21 January-4 February 1922 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Light and Power Department, weekly and monthly reports, 11-18 February 1922 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous customers' power bills, correspondence concerning, 1918-1919 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Motor Transit Corporation, monthly reports, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Other states' utility rates (chart), 1917 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Railway and Light and Power Departments, division of expenses, 1912 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Report on Determination of Original Cost of Electric Plant as of 1 January 1937, submitted 1942 (Box 29, Folder 35)